http://www.nelsongranite.com/6/privacy-policy

Your Personal Information
We may ask you to give us information that personally identifies you (’Personal Information’). For example, we may request Personal Information when you download evaluation software, email us, or ask us to forward information to you. We use your Personal Information primarily to:
Provide you with information about Nelson Granite's products, services, news and events allow you to purchase and or download products, and gather broad demographic information about user trends.
If you choose not to provide Personal Information, you may still use our web sites anonymously. Only the domain name from which you access the Internet, the Internet address and the date and time you access our web sites are logged. Nelson Granite uses this information to analyze trends and to measure the number of visitors to our web sites.
Passwords
In order to bring you more personalized services, we may ask you to establish one or more passwords to gain access to certain services or sections in this site. You are solely responsible for the control and use of each password you create.
Use of Cookies
Some of our web pages use ’cookies’. A cookie is a small file that a web site may send to your browser. This file is then stored on your hard drive. A cookie does not contain any Personal Information, but it does enable Nelson Granite to build a better web site by recording how and when guests use our site and to better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, but if you do, you might not be able to take full advantage of our site.
Contacting Nelson Granite
Please feel free to contact Nelson Granite by emailing us if:
You have concerns or comments about Nelson Granite's Privacy Policy and related practices.
You would like to stop receiving information from Nelson Granite
You want to correct or update your Personal Information.
Designed by:
Dubyts Communications Inc.
